Hit enter to search or ESC to close

Get 16% Off Gutter Helmet Today!\*

REQUEST A FREE ESTIMATE
-----------------------

Name(Required)

 First Last

Phone(Required)

Email(Required)

ZIP Code(Required)

Comments

This field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.

Δ

PRIVACY POLICY
--------------

The Gibraltar group of companies, including Prospiant, Air Vent, Terrasmart, HIG, D.S. Brown, and MAPS (referred to generally as “us” or “we”) recognizes that your privacy is important. This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) discloses the privacy practices of Gibraltar’s website and mobile applications, as well as related products and services we may offer to you (collectively referred to as the “Services”). This Policy covers how Personal Data that we receive or collect about you is used or shared.  By using our Site and Services, you agree to the terms of this Policy as they may be amended from time to time. We treat any data that identifies you, or reasonably can be linked to you, as “Personal Data.”  Data that has been de-identified or aggregated so that it cannot reasonably be linked to you is not Personal Data, and we may use that data for any purpose.  When we maintain and use de-identified data, we do not attempt to re-identify the data. [Our California Notice of Collection](#privacy-california) is available below.

1. [Personal Data We Collect From You](#privacy-data)
2. [How We Obtain Your Personal Data](#privacy-obtain-data)
3. [Our Use of Personal Data](#privacy-use-data)
4. [Our Sharing of Personal Data](#privacy-share-data)
5. [Use of Cookies](#privacy-cookies)
6. [Security of Your Personal Data](#privacy-data-security)
7. [Third Party Websites and Applications](#privacy-third-party)
8. [Jurisdiction Specific Provisions](#privacy-jurisdiction)
    1. [California Privacy Notice](#privacy-california)
    2. [Privacy Rights in Nevada](#privacy-nevada)
    3. [Data Subjects Outside of the United States](#privacy-outside-usa)
9. [Personal Data Concerning Children](#privacy-data-children)
10. [Updates to the Policy](#privacy-updates)
11. [Contact Us](#privacy-contact)

### 1\. Personal Data We Collect From You

We may collect the following Personal Data about you:

* **Contact Information,** such as name, postal address, phone numbers, and email address.
* **Internet or Similar Network Activity,** such as your IP address and activity on our Site, as well as your browsing history on our Site, interaction with our advertising and other communications.
* **Commercial Information**, such as information relating to your purchases and services, and purchasing or consuming histories, tendencies or interests.
* **IP Location Information,** such as information regarding IP Addresses collected automatically when you access our Site.
* **Financial Information,** such as payment account information for our Services.
* **Photo or Video Information**, such as if customers provide photos or videos to us related to our products.
* **Demographic Information**, such as age or birthday, income range, marital status, race or gender.
* **Education Information**, such as a customer’s education level collected when purchasing a product or service.
* **Inferences,** such as by using the data described above to build customer profiles to better serve customers and direct relevant information to customers.

### 2\. How We Obtain Your Personal Data

We obtain your Personal Data in the following ways:

* **From You**:  We obtain most of the Personal Data that we collect about you from you when you interact with our Site or Services, including when you contact and communicate with us via forms contained on our Site, complete surveys, register for warranties, or attend events that we sponsor.
* **From Service Providers**: We may obtain Personal Data about you from our service providers.
* **From Third Parties**.  We may obtain information about you from third parties, including dealers and operators of events or trade shows.  For example, you may register for an event or work with a dealer of our products, and that information may be shared with us.  We also may receive information from third parties who provide contact information of potential customers.

### 3\. Our Use of Personal Data

We may use your Personal Data as follows:

* **Provide Our Products and Services:**  We use Personal Data to furnish our Services, including to process and fulfill your purchases of our Services and to improve the quality, safety and security of the Services.
* **Communicate with You:**  We use Personal Data to respond to communications, contact you about your transactions, provide other relevant information, and request information or feedback.
* **Marketing and Analytics:**  We use Personal Data to promote our Services.
* **Personalize Your Experience**:  We utilize Personal Data regarding your use of our Site, including to personalize and enhance your experiences.
* **Internal Research**:  We use Personal Data to conduct internal research to develop, improve or repair our products, services or technology.
* **Security or Fraud Prevention**:  We use Personal Data to: (1) prevent, detect, protect against, or respond to security incidents, (2) preserve the integrity or security of systems, or (3) otherwise protect our rights.
* **Legal Compliance**:  We may use Personal Data to comply with applicable law or to comply with a lawful governmental request.

We strive to retain your Personal Data only for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which we obtained the information or as otherwise required by law.

### 4\. Our Sharing of Personal Data

We may share Personal Data with service providers who act on our behalf, our partners, or others operating at your direction or where legally necessary or appropriate.

* **Legal Affiliates:**  We may share all of the types of data that you collect with our subsidiaries and legal affiliates.
* **Service Providers**:  We engage third parties to act as our service providers and perform certain tasks on our behalf in connection with our Site and Services.  The tasks performed by service providers include: (1) processing and storing Personal Data, (2) assisting with marketing communications and advertising, (3) customer service assistance; and (4) providing technology services, including assisting with our Site and providing analytics services.  We may share all types of Personal Data described above with service providers, although in most cases we only share identifiers.
* **Partners**:  We may partner with other companies to provide services and other offerings.  For example, we may make available your Personal Data with our dealer network to provide products or services that may interest you.
* **Other Legal Purposes**:  We also may share Personal Data: (1) with your consent, (2) to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process or otherwise as required or allowed by law or the competent governmental or judicial authorities; (3) to cooperate with law enforcement, government or regulatory entities, and safety or investigation authorities; (4) to establish or preserve a legal claim or defense; or (5) as part of a corporate restructuring, sale of assets, merger or divestiture.

### 5\. Use of Cookies

Like many commercial websites, we analyze how visitors use our Site with “cookie” technology. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer when you access our website and allows us to recognize you each time you visit the website. We may use cookies to (1) enhance or personalize your website usage and experience; (2) monitor website usage; and (3) improve the website and our services, including providing you with interest-based ads.  We may work with service providers that help us track, collect and analyze this information.  We may combine the information we collect through cookies with other information we have collected from you or information from other sources. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you choose, you can set your browser to reject cookies or you can manually delete individual cookies or all of the cookies on your computer by following your browser’s help file directions.  Please refer to your browser instructions or to www.aboutcookies.org to learn more about how to adjust of modify your browser settings.  However, if your browser is set to reject cookies or you manually delete cookies, you may have some trouble accessing and using some of the pages and features on our website. Please note that browser-management tools for cookies are outside of our control, and we cannot guarantee their effectiveness. Many advertisers and service providers that perform advertising-related services for us and third parties participate in voluntary programs that provide tools to opt-out of such interest-based advertising such as the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (“DAA”) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. To learn more about how you can exercise certain choices regarding interest-based advertising for DAA members, visit [https://youradchoices.com/](https://youradchoices.com/ "Go to website YourAdChoices.com"), and [https://www.aboutads.info/appchoices](https://www.aboutads.info/appchoices "Go to website AboutAds.info") for information on the DAA’s opt-out program for mobile apps. Some of these companies also are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”). To learn more about the NAI and your opt-out options for their members, see [https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ "Go to website NetworkAdvertising.org"). You can also go to [https://help.adroll.com/hc/en-us/requests/new](https://help.adroll.com/hc/en-us/requests/new "Go to website Help.AdRoll.com") to adjust your advertising preferences with our provider AdRoll. Your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit a “Do Not Track” signal to online services you visit. Note, however, there is no consensus among industry participants as to what “Do Not Track” means in this context. Like many online services, we currently do not alter our practices when we receive a “Do Not Track” signal from a visitor’s browser. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” you can visit [https://www.allaboutdnt.com](https://www.allaboutdnt.com/ "Go to website AllAboutDNT.com"), but we are not responsible for the completeness or accuracy of this third-party information.

### 6\. Security of Your Personal Data

We maintain reasonable physical, technical and administrative security measures to reduce the risk of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, and disclosure.  Please note, however, that no security measures are perfectly secure, and we are unable to guarantee the security of your Personal Data.

### 7\. Third Party Websites and Applications

Our Site may contain links to websites or applications hosted by third parties.  This Policy only applies to websites and applications within our control and does not apply to any third party sources.  Any data collected through third party websites or applications shall be subject to the privacy practices of the third party, and you should review the privacy policies of these third parties prior to sharing any data.

### 8\. Jurisdiction Specific Provisions

* #### a. California Privacy Notice
    
    This section describes how Gibraltar Collects, uses and discloses Personal Information of California residents who interact with our Site. We provide this CCPA Notice pursuant to the California Consumer Privacy Act, as amended by the California Privacy Rights Act (the “CCPA”) and as a supplement to Gibraltar’s other privacy policies or notices. In the event of a conflict between this CCPA Notice and the Privacy Policy, this CCPA Notice shall govern as to the rights of California consumers as defined in the CCPA (“Consumers”) under the CCPA. Capitalized terms that are used in this CCPA Notice shall have the meaning given to them in the Privacy Policy unless otherwise noted.
    
    #### _Personal Information We Collect and Why We Collect It_
    
    “**Personal Information**” or “**PI**” means information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with you. Within the past 12 months, we have collected and may collect the following categories of PI about California Consumers Contacts:
    
    | **Category of Personal Information** | **Categories of Sources from which Information was Collected** | **Purposes for Collection** |
    | --- | --- | --- |
    | **Identifiers**, including real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, IP address, email address, account name, social security number, driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers | Directly from you Automatically when you use our websites Service Providers that help us to run our business Data Analytics Providers Ad Networks, Social Media Platforms, and other marketing or advertising partners | To provide our products and services To communicate with you To support our website For marketing purposes For analytics, research and development, or to otherwise improve our business To comply with applicable laws and regulations To detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity |
    | **Personal records described in Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e)**, including name, signature, social security number, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, passport number, driver’s license or state identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information | Directly from you Service Providers that help us to run our business Data Analytics Providers Ad Networks, Social Media Platforms, and other marketing or advertising partners Data Brokers | To provide our products and services To communicate with you To facilitate services youprovide To support our website For marketing purposes For analytics, research and development, or to otherwise improve our business To comply with applicable laws and regulations To detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity |
    | **Characteristics of protected classifications** under California or federal law, including age and date of birth, race, ancestry, ethnic origin, sex, gender, sexual orientation, gender identity, religion or creed, military or veteran status, medical condition, genetic information, disability, marital status | Directly from you Data Brokers | To provide our products and services For marketing purposes For analytics, research and development, or to otherwise improve our business To comply with applicable laws and regulations To detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity |
    | **Commercial information,** including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies | Directly from you Service Providers that help us to run our business Data Analytics Providers Ad Networks, and other marketing or advertising partners Data Brokers | To provide our products and services To support our website For marketing purposes For analytics, research and development, or to otherwise improve our business To comply with applicable laws and regulations To detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity |
    | **Internet or other electronic network activity information,** including browsing history, search history, and information regarding your interactions with our websites, applications, or advertisements | Automatically when you use our website Service Providers that help us to run our business Data Analytics Providers Ad Networks, Social Media Platforms, and other marketing or advertising partners | To support our website For marketing purposes For analytics, research and development, or to otherwise improve our business To detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity |
    | **Geolocation data** | Automatically when you use our website Ad Networks and other marketing or advertising partners Directly from you | To provide our products and services To support our website For marketing purposes For analytics, research and development, or to otherwise improve our business To detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity |
    | **Audio, electronic, visual, or similar information, including**, including photographs, audio, and video recordings | Directly from you (e.g., when you speak with us on a recorded phone line or engage with us via teleconferencing) | To provide our products and services To communicate with you For analytics, research and development, or to otherwise improve our business To detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity |
    | **Professional or employment-related information** Information relating to professional licenses, training,  and membership in professional organizations; | Directly from you | To communicate with you For analytics, research and development, or to otherwise improve our business To comply with applicable laws and regulations To detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity |
    | **Inferences** used to create a profile reflecting someone’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes | Drawn from the other categories of Personal Information we collect Data Analytics Providers Ad Networks and other marketing or advertising partners Data Brokers | To support our website For analytics, research and development, or to otherwise improve our business To detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity |
    
    #### _The categories of PI we may collect include the following categories of Sensitive PI_
    
    | **Category of Sensitive Personal Information** | **Categories of Sources from which Information was Collected** | **Purposes for Collection** |
    | --- | --- | --- |
    | Personal Information that reveals an account log-in, financial account, debit card, or credit card number in combination with any required security or access code, password, or credentials allowing access to an account | Directly from you | To provide our products and services To detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity |
    | Precise geolocation (location within a radius of 1,850 feet). | Automatically when you use our website Directly from you. | To provide our products and services To provide our products and services To detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity |
    
    In addition, we may Collect, use and disclose your PI as required or permitted by applicable law, or as directed by you, in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Additionally, each of the above referenced categories of PI may be shared with government agencies, other third parties as required by law or compelled by legal process, to other parties at the Consumer’s request, and to assignees as part of a merger or asset sale. Further, we may Deidentify or aggregate your PI, and as permitted by applicable law, we do not treat De-identified or Aggregate Consumer Information as PI. Similarly, as permitted by the CCPA, we may not treat publicly available data as PI.
    
    #### _How Long We Keep Your Personal Information_
    
    We keep the categories of Personal Information described above for as long as necessary or permitted for the purposes described in this Notice or otherwise authorized by law. This generally means holding PI for as long as one of the following apply:
    
    * Your PI is reasonably necessary to manage our operations, to manage your relationship with us, or to satisfy another purpose for which we collected the information;
    * Your PI is reasonably necessary to carry out a disclosed purpose that is reasonably compatible with the context in which the PI was collected;
    * The PI is reasonably necessary to protect or defend our rights or property (which will generally relate to applicable laws that limit actions in a particular case); or
    * We are otherwise required or permitted to keep your information by applicable laws or regulations.
    
    Where PI is used for more than one purpose, we will retain it until the purpose with the latest period expires. For more information about our retention policies, please contact us using the contact details below.
    
    #### _How We Disclose, Share, and Sell Personal Information_
    
    We may disclose Personal Information as indicated below. The first chart shows the categories of Personal Information we disclose to our service providers and contractors for a business or commercial purpose. Although we do not sell Personal Information in exchange for money, some of our advertising practices or other disclosures of PI to third parties under circumstances where the third parties may use the information for their own purposes may be classified as “sales” or “sharing” under California law. The second chart shows the categories of Personal Information we may share for purposes of cross-context behavioral advertising or otherwise “sell,” as that term is defined under California law. We do not have actual knowledge that we sell or share the PI of California residents under 16 years of age.
    
    #### _Disclosures for a Business or Commercial Purpose_
    
    | **Category of Personal Information** | **Categories of Recipients to which Information was Disclosed** | **Purposes for Disclosure** |
    | --- | --- | --- |
    | Identifiers | Service Providers that help us to run our business (technical support, analytics, communications and marketing services, web hosting and monitoring services, among other) Government entities | Providing our products and services Communicating with you Supporting our website including debugging and repair of errors Short-term, transient use, including, but not limited to, non-personalized advertising For analytics, research and development, or to otherwise improve our business Ensuring security and integrity, and to detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity To comply with applicable laws and regulations |
    | Personal records | Service Providers that help us to run our business (technical support, analytics, communications and marketing services, , web hosting and monitoring services, among other) Government entities | Providing our products and services Communicating with you Supporting our website including debugging and repair of errors Short-term, transient use, including, but not limited to, non-personalized advertising For analytics, research and development, or to otherwise improve our business Ensuring security and integrity, and to detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity To comply with applicable laws and regulations |
    | Characteristics of protected classifications | Government entities | Providing our products and services To comply with applicable laws and regulations |
    | Commercial information | Service Providers that help us to run our business (e.g.,  analytics, communications and marketing services, promotions, call centers, and event-related services, among other) Government entities | Providing our products and services Communicating with you Short-term, transient use, including, but not limited to, non-personalized advertising For analytics, research and development, or to otherwise improve our business Ensuring security and integrity, and to detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity To comply with applicable laws and regulations |
    | Internet or other electronic network activity information | Service Providers that help us to run our business (e.g., technical support, analytics, communications and marketing services, and web hosting and monitoring services) Operating systems, internet service providers, and platforms | Supporting our website Short-term, transient use, including, but not limited to, non-personalized advertising For analytics, research and development, or to otherwise improve our business Ensuring security and integrity, and to detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity |
    | Geolocation | Service Providers that help us to run our business (e.g., technical support, analytics, communications and marketing services, and web hosting and monitoring services, among other) Government entities | Supporting our website, including debugging and repair of errors Short-term, transient use, including, but not limited to, non-personalized advertising For analytics, research and development, or to otherwise improve our business Ensuring security and integrity, and to detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity |
    | Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information | Service Providers that help us to run our business (e.g., technical support, analytics, communications and marketing services) Government entities | Providing our products and services Communicating with you Short-term, transient use, including, but not limited to, non-personalized advertising For analytics, research and development, or to otherwise improve our business Ensuring security and integrity, and to detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity To comply with applicable laws and regulations |
    | Professional or employment-related information | Service Providers that help us to run our business (technical support, analytics, communications and marketing services, , call centers, among other) Government entities | Providing our products and services Communicating with you Short-term, transient use, including, but not limited to, non-personalized advertising For analytics, research and development, or to otherwise improve our business Ensuring security and integrity, and to detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity To comply with applicable laws and regulations |
    | **Sensitive Personal Information** |     |     |
    | Social security, driver’s license, state identification card, or passport number | Service Providers that help us to run our business Government entities | Providing our products and services Ensuring security and integrity, and to detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity To comply with applicable laws and regulations |
    | Account log-in, financial account, debit card, or credit card number in combination with any required security or access code, password, or credentials allowing access to an account | Service Providers that help us to run our business (e.g., technical support, and web hosting and monitoring services) | Supporting our website including debugging and repair of errors Ensuring security and integrity, and to detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity |
    | Precise geolocation | Service Providers that help us to run our business (e.g., technical support, analytics, and web hosting and monitoring services) | Providing our products and services Supporting our including debugging and repair of errors Ensuring security and integrity, and to detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity |
    | Personal Information collected and analyzed concerning a person’s health | Service Providers that help us to run our business | Providing our products and services Ensuring security and integrity, and to detect and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity |
    
    #### _Sales and Sharing of Personal Information_
    
    | **Category of Personal Information** | **Categories of Third Parties to which Information was Sold or Shared** | **Purposes for Selling / Sharing** |
    | --- | --- | --- |
    | Identifiers | Ad networks, search and social media platforms, and other online advertising partners | Cross-context behavioral advertising |
    | Commercial information |
    | Internet or other electronic network activity information |
    | Geolocation data |
    
    #### _Rights Relating to Your Personal Information_
    
    If you are a California Consumer, you have the right to submit requests related to your PI as described below. **Right to Know**. You have the right to know what Personal Information we have collected about you, which includes:
    
    1. The categories of Personal Information we have collected about you, including
        1. The categories of sources from which the Personal Information was Collected
        2. Our business or commercial purposes for Collecting, Selling, or Sharing Personal Information
        3. The categories of recipients to which we disclose Personal Information
        4. The categories of Personal Information that we Sold, and for each category identified, the categories of Third Parties to which we Sold that particular category of Personal Information
        5. The categories of Personal Information that we disclosed for a Business Purpose, and for each category identified, the categories of recipients to which we disclosed that particular category of Personal Information
    2. A copy of the specific pieces of Personal Information we have Collected about you
    
    **Right to Request Deletion**. You have the right, subject to certain conditions and exceptions, to request that we delete your PI that we have Collected directly from you and are maintaining. If you prefer to exercise more limited control of your PI, you may cancel or modify the email marketing communications you receive from us by following the instructions contained within our promotional emails. **Right to Request Correction of Inaccurate Information**.If you believe that PI that we maintain about you is inaccurate, you have the right, subject to certain restrictions, to request that we correct that information. **Right to Opt Out of Sales and Sharing of Personal Information**. The CCPA gives you the right to opt out of the Sale of your PI and to request that we do not Share your PI for cross-context behavioral advertising purposes. We do not sell or share personal information as defined by the CCPA **Right to Limit Use and Disclosure of Sensitive Personal Information**. The CCPA gives you the right to limit the use and disclosure of your Sensitive Personal Information. We only use and disclose sensitive personal information in ways that are not subject to limitation, such as uses and disclosures that are reasonably necessary to provide our products and services, or as needed: to ensure security and integrity; to prevent fraud or illegal activity; for physical safety; for short-term, transient use, including for non-personalized advertising; to perform services on behalf of the business; and to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by us, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance such services or devices. **Rights Related to Automated Decision-Making**. The CCPA gives you the right to opt out of certain automated decision-making, including profiling. We do not engage in automated decision making that is subject to the right to opt out. **Right to Non-Discrimination for the Exercise of Your Privacy Rights**. If you choose to exercise any of your privacy rights under the CCPA, you will not receive discriminatory treatment by us. **How to Exercise Your Rights.** To exercise any of the rights outlined in the preceding section, please email us at: [privacyinformation@gibraltar1.com](mailto:privacyinformation@gibraltar1.com "Email privacyinformation@gibraltar1.com"), or call us at [(888) 264-5708](tel:18882645708 "Call (888) 264-5708"). **Through An Authorized Agent**. An authorized agent may submit a request on your behalf.  We may require the authorized agent to provide proof that you gave the agent signed permission to submit the request. Depending on the type of request, we may also require that you verify your identity directly with us. **Verification Process**.  Whether you submit your request to us directly or through an authorized agent, we must first verify your identity.  The information we need to verify your identity will differ depending on the type of request and our relationship with you.  Please note that, if you submit a request to know, request to delete, or request to correct, you may be asked to provide PI that we will match against our records to verify your identity. In some cases, we may also use third-party identity verification services to verify your identity.
    
    #### _California Shine the Light_
    
    Separately from the CCPA, the California Shine the Light law permits customers in California to request certain details about how their personal information is “shared” with third parties as defined in the Shine the Light law, and in some cases affiliates, if personal information is shared for those third parties’ or affiliates’ own direct marketing purposes. We share personal information with third parties or affiliates for those third parties’ or affiliates’ own direct marketing purposes. Californians may request information about our personal information sharing by contacting us at [privacyinformation@gibraltar1.com](mailto:privacyinformation@gibraltar1.com "Email privacyinformation@gibraltar1.com"). Please include “California Shine the Light Request” in the subject line and in the body of your message. Please note that “Shine the Light” rights and CCPA rights are granted by different laws and must be exercised separately.

* #### b. Privacy Rights in Nevada
    
    Under Nevada law, Nevada residents may opt out of the sale of certain “covered information” collected by operators of websites or online services. We currently do not sell covered information, as “sale” is defined by such law, and we don’t have plans to sell this information

* #### c. Data Subjects Outside of the United States
    
    Our Services are only directed at users in the United States and all personal information or personal data collected through or in connection our Services is processed in accordance with applicable United States law.

### 9\. Personal Data Concerning Children

Our Site is not intended for anyone under the age of 16.  We do not knowingly collect Personal Data from individuals under the age of 16.

### 10\. Updates to the Policy

We may update this Policy periodically as we offer new products and services, and as our business, technology, and laws change. You can determine when this Policy was last revised by referring to the “Last updated” reference below.  Any changes will become effective upon posting of the revised Policy.

### 11\. Contact Us

[privacyinformation@gibraltar1.com](mailto:privacyinformation@gibraltar1.com "Email privacyinformation@gibraltar1.com") Last updated:  June 30th, 2023.

© Gutter Helmet.

\*\*Discount off dealer list price as to product plus professional installation, to be applied at time of contract execution by representative. Cannot be combined with other offers; applies to new Gutter Helmet purchase only. Participating dealers only. See dealer for details. Purchase documents must be entered into on or before . Offer must be presented at time of estimate. Offer subject to change without notice. Minimum 100 LF purchase. Gutter Helmet is not responsible for any typos. Void where prohibited by law. [Privacy Policy](https://www.gutterhelmet.com/privacy-policy)

Help Water Flow & Cash Flow! Get $250 Off Gutter Helmet Today!

"\*" indicates required fields

Name\*

First Name  Last Name 

Email\*

Phone\*

ZIP Code\*

**Contact Disclaimer**  
I'm interested in possibly having Gutter Helmet on my home, by submitting this online request, which I agree is my signature, I'd also like to learn about Gutter Helmet products and sales. I understand you may use an auto-dialing phone system to contact me via phone, email or text. I understand consent is not required and that I can opt-out at any time, including (for texts) by replying "STOP" to cancel; "HELP" for help. I agree to Gutter Helmet's **Privacy Policy** and **Terms and Conditions.** Message and data rates apply.

Δ

×

\*\*Discount off dealer list price as to product plus professional installation, to be applied at time of contract execution by representative. Cannot be combined with other offers; applies to new Gutter Helmet purchase only. Participating dealers only. See dealer for details. Purchase documents must be entered into on or before . Offer must be presented at time of estimate. Offer subject to change without notice. Minimum 100 LF purchase. Gutter Helmet is not responsible for any typos. Void where prohibited by law.

×

Please note that we use cookies necessary for the functioning of our website.[I Understand](#)[Privacy policy](https://www.gutterhelmet.com/privacy-policy/)
